Keep running along, watch as we pass by,
as we raise our flag up high in the sky.
Alright,
here we go now, sailing through the
endless ocean, facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure nobody has
ever got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep believing in our
dreams, And let our heart lead the way!
Then once we got all that,
All there's left is to go!
When we face, The dark and stormy weather!
Keep the pace!
We'll link our hearts together!
Then I'm sure we'll make it through!
No matter what!
Keep running along!
Start raising our flag!
As we journey on!
Though our chances are close to
none, We won't back down from anyone!
Let's start off the chase,
let's start off the chase!
Toward our own dreams,
while keeping the pace!
With a compass pointing to our goal!
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world!
Start me off!
Keep running along, keep running along!
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top!
There's no way that we'll ever quit!
We'll keep heading for tomorrow!
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase!
I see through your eyes
what we'll have to face!
All the memories will stay in our hearts!
We'll never let them go!
Brand new world!
Let's start me up!
So this mirage trick of
yours only one of you
is actually real you
got it there's only one
me The other four are
nothing more than illusions
distorted reflections
from the freezing air!
Simple illusions huh that's quite
the mysterious and elegant tactic!
Regardless,
I fail to see how Something that consists
of thin air can pose any threat to me!
So in other words, deceptive
Misdirection must be your goal!
Well, aren't you smart?
You got some confidence back
and it's not Cute at all!
Thunder charge!
Only one of the five figures
before you is the real me,
obviously your Point
you'll see only 20% % of
these thunderball attacks
are the real deal!
Good luck dodging!
Damn it! Which one?
I need to guard my...
100 % real power, though.
I told you, didn't I?
Your arrogance is reckless.
You just got hit with the new
and improved climb attack.
A single thunderball
attack is that powerful.
The next attack will be stronger,
and it's going to end this.
That's a rather bold promise.
And you say I'm arrogant.
It's not a promise.
It's a forecast.
Maybe you haven't realized this, but the
weather in this room is under my control.
I don't see how that's going
to make any difference for you,
since I'm still a master
of the six powers.
Now behave!
What? That was a fake?
You've only got a 20 % chance
of finding the real me.
In today's forecast,
although we have a stable pressure system,
you should be on the lookout for
small storm clouds and violent winds.
And there's a 100 % chance of a strong
bolt of lightning piercing your chest.
You can expect paralysis of the
heart to follow shortly after.
Dark cloud tempo!
I've already shown you how easily I
can protect myself against lightning.
What makes you think it'll work now?
Although that shell of yours
may be good for blocking,
you can't move at all
when you're using it.
You don't take me seriously.
You really think you can puncture
my soap shell with an attack?
Well then, soap sheet!
I don't need to find the
real you to win this battle.
I'll just drench everything in the
room with a wave of relaxing bubbles.
Sheep Clowns!
Turn away!
I'm a goner if I get hit by that again.
Clearly the real you will be the
one left writhing on the floor.
Do you think I'm gonna let that happen?
Cyclotism!
She's blowing the bubbles back with wind!
I'll assume the one that's still running
for her precious life is the real one.
Finger crystal!
Well, I'll be.
I guess you're not just another illusion.
I'm done playing this game.
I'm gonna fill you with more holes
than a pair of my fishnet stockings.
You weren't listening
to me earlier, were you?
You'd have to be a fool to
disregard a navigator's forecast.
A thunderbolt will burst from the
clouds and connect with the climate act.
Now!
Not again.
That's our last tempo!
You might be remarkably strong, but I can
predict the weather, and I'm never wrong.
My friends are waiting for me.
I'll be taking your key now.
Dear Gorilla, bring it all in!
Franky, what the - what are
you doing climbing up the wall?
I don't want to get into it.
That rampaging, beefed-up Dear
Gorilla come through this way.
Dear what?
Chopper? I guess.
I'd just call him Dear Gorilla.
Yeah, he did.
What the heck happened to him?
I've never seen him like that before.
Got me.
I was going to ask you the same thing.
Can't usually transform like that
Not that I know of that's the first
time I've seen anything like it.
Well, that's not good I was hoping you
might have some experience dealing with him
No other choice guess.
We'll just have to kill him
Yeah, you ever say that again, then
I'll have no choice but to kill you.
Okay, sure never again message received
Oh, by the way, nice work
in here. I'm impressed.
You're able to take her down I'm
pretty sure she's got the key we need.
The number two key, that is.
Oh, yeah.
Give me a sec.
I was just searching for it.
Key? Key?
Where could she have hidden it?
Wow, that's some scandalous action.
Another giant monster!
How many of these Zoan-type power holders
have they got on this damn island?
Wait, you sure that's another CP9 agent?
He looks kind of familiar for some reason.
What? Chopper!
Back off, Chopper! It's us!
Hey, Chopper, don't kill me!
How do we know that
thing really is Chopper?
Why the hell doesn't he recognize us?
I've got no idea, but that is Chopper!
Who else has antlers and
wears a hat like that?
Then what are we supposed to do here?
You think he has the key?
No, but what does it matter?
Let's face it, we're gonna die!
I don't know, something
doesn't seem right.
He looks like he's the one
about to keel over and die.
Seems like all the life is
being sucked right out of him.
Well, what's wrong with him?
I have no idea.
But being in that form must use
up an enormous amount of energy.
So then, what? huh?
How he's supposed to help him like
this and what about those two?
And where's the key?
Where is the damn key?
I don't know about the
key, but I can guess.
What happened to him?
He probably put his life on the line
fighting against someone incredibly strong.
And when it still wasn't enough,
he turned into that. And now!
Who is this enormous beast?
And why is he interrupting our fight?
Especially when the buster
calls right around the corner.
He's a damn pain.
Must be part of their dumbass crew.
If they're in our way...
Then we eliminate them.
He looks a bit sick.
Then that just makes him easier prey.
They're going after Chopper!
Stiffen your back.
You are still my sword.
Whoa, hold on!
We're doing this again?!
36-caliber Phoenix!
You bastard!
Step aside, you guys! It's you.
Hey, hold it!
What do you think you're doing?
The deer monster is on our side!
I know what I'm doing!
Shut up and move!
This is the only way there is
to deal with power holders.
Have one weakness!
I'll knock him into the sea!
Sorry pal, but this is for your own good.
That's the last straw, Franky!
You're not gonna get away with this!
Nobody treats my friends that way!
It's okay, guys.
We came up with this plan together.
Why are they attacking their own crew?
Doesn't even make any sense. I don't know.
They're really getting
on my nerves, though.
You finally managed to
free yourselves, huh?
You better stop laughing and
start running you blew your
only chance to kill me and
you're not getting another!
It's my turn and I'm taking you all down!
The entire world government?
The buster calls gonna wipe
us out along with the pirates!
You get back here, Nico Robin!
Even if you make it out of this tunnel,
all you'll find are your friend's corpses!
I've had enough of this nonsense.
Let's teach her a lesson, Funkfreed.
Luffy is just up ahead.
But don't kill her, understood?
Ivory dart!
Come on!
Idiot!
You will never escape!
Don't underestimate me!
Now come along, you wench
through the gate of dreams.
He's finally back to normal.
Doesn't look like he's dead.
This is weird.
Not even his friends do how to
handle this guy after he changed.
Do you want to get Nico
Robin back or not? I do!
Robin!
Well, whatever.
At least you managed to take
out one of the CP9 guys.
Kind of lame how you turned into that
giant thing and tried to kill me?
But if your friends are willing to stand
up for you, then I won't hold a grudge!
We better get moving.
Now that I think about
it even if we hurt how do
we get to the gates of
justice without a bridge?
It's you guys?
Wait you found a tunnel that
leads to the Gates of Justice!
Sure did, and we'll take you
right through if you like.
I show Granny.
She's down there now.
All right, then.
Let's get moving.
I'll fill you in on the plan after
we meet up with the old lady.
Got it? Roger.
He's unconscious, but I'm pretty
sure he's going to be okay.
No time to waste.
I need to get these keys to Nico Robin
before they take her through that gate.
You guys grab the deer
and follow me, all right?
Yeah.
We don't have a choice that's
the only way we can stop Chopper.
Oh and here take these.
Once we get him back to normal you'll need
to get the number 3 and 4 keys to Robin.
One of them should be able
to unlock her restraints.
Soon as you get the cuffs off
call me on this transponder.
Snail I swipe from Blondie right.
Meanwhile I'll take this
key and get the cuffs off.
Zoro and Nose King.
Seems like a solid plan, but
what do we do after that?
Even if we're able to free
everyone and rescue Nico Robin,
that drawbridge is still locked up.
We'll be running around this damn tower
with no way to get back to Annie's lobby.
We're stuck here.
Yeah.
There's the Buster Call to deal with, too.
If we tried going back the way
we came, we'd get blown to bits.
So?
What do you think?
The choice is pretty clear now, isn't it?
A waterfall of death behind us?
A mysterious path ahead?
Which way would you go?
The mysterious path ahead, of course.
Exactly.
So once we've freed everyone
and we're done in this tower,
we'll meet at the Gates of Justice.
After that, just leave everything...
To you? To luck.
Oh, that's just great.
Come on.
We've wasted quite a bit of time here.
Damn right you have.
I can't believe you two.
How can you be screwing
around at a time like this?
Because!
He wouldn't stop acting like an idiot!
You're both acting like idiots!
Hurry up and get those keys!
Tempest kick?
Strike guard!
Just as I instructed!
Nice going, Zoro! Fight! Zoro!
You guys fight too, damn it!
That long neck of yours...
...sure looks like a weak spot to me.
Sorry, but that's where you're wrong.
The abilities I've gained allow me
to freely control my neck with ease.
Plus, I have a new attack.
Nose pistol!
Whoa!
We're all the way over here and
I can still feel the shockwave!
A square-shaped hole?
That's an impressive nose!
Even more so than sniper sauce!
Sniper sauce? What the hell?
It lay out the nose, got it?
At any rate,
looks like Kaku's really getting the
hang of using his Devil Fruit abilities.
Fast learner.
All right, Wolf, I'm the one you've
got to deal with now, so bring it on!
Huh?
Don't get so worked up.
Listen, you guys want to
save your friend, right?
Yeah, that's right.
And I'm going to take your key to do it.
Then go save her while
you still can. What?
You heard me.
Take that key and go save your friend.
I don't get it. Why?
I don't like killing people.
The sight of bloodshed
makes me sick to my stomach.
I'm a pacifist.
Oh, uh, okay then, I'll just,
uh, take this key and, uh...
No, look out!
Ten-figure pistol!
Never let your guard down.
I'm a wolf, understand?
I outsmart my prey and then I eat it. No!
AHHHHH! Who's up?
Damn it.
What am I...
What am I doing?
Ahhhh!
That mask can't hide your stupidity!
Why don't you just run around screaming
and crying like you did earlier?
You were great at that!
Don't you make fun of me!
Huh?
We don't have time for crap like this!
New weapon, Kabuto!
Special attack, Sunflower Star!
Wow, a fireworks show.
No, Usopp!
Moonwalk!
Leave him alone!
just like i promised i'll
kill you quickly there won't
be any pain it's too bad
really you were so much better
off when you were connected
to that green-haired shepherd
over there but since this
little lamb has wandered off on
his own things are a bit
different now you're nothing
but a tasty morsel for the
big scary wolf this is the end
let him go please don't kill
him keep your key we don't
need it you stupid girl you're
gonna be the next one to die
Oh no, and now it's over.
Who's up?
Who the hell are you?
I'm the hunter.